
export const questionsColumn1 = [
    { amount: 100, question: "This popular childrens game. when you caught moving you'll be eliminated or you'll be sent back to starting line. and played in Squid Game netflix series", isDone: false, answer: "Red Light/ Green Light" },
    { amount: 200, question: "This popular video game series was developed by Game Freak and first released in japan in 1996", isDone: false, answer: "Pokémon"  },
    { amount: 300, question: "This movie is based on life story by Frank Abagnale Jr. and it was played by Leonardo DiCaprio and Tom Hanks", isDone: false, answer: "Catch me if you can" },
    { amount: 400, question: "Japanese term for this fish Maguro (mah-goo-roh) or hon-maguro, and this fish in japan just sold for a of record $3 million in a auction", isDone: false, answer: "Bluefin Tuna" }
]
  
export const questionsColumn2 = [
    { amount: 100, question: "It song recorded by English singer-songwriter Adele for her second studio album, 21. It is the lead single and opening track on the album", isDone: false, answer: "Rolling in the deep by Adele" },
    { amount: 200, question: "This actor plays the lead role in Pirates of the Caribbean and Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", isDone: false, answer: "Johnny Depp" },
    { amount: 300, question: "This massive lake is considered as deepest lake in the world and it lies on mountainous Russian region of Siberia, north of the Mongolian border", isDone: false, answer: "Lake Baikal" },
    { amount: 400, question: "This deep space telescope is set into space this year and it will take place of Hubble telescope", isDone: false, answer: "James Webb Space Telescope (JWST)" }
]
  
export const questionsColumn3 = [
    { amount: 100, question: "This country has eleven timezones", isDone: false, answer: "Russia" },
    { amount: 200, question: "This country has a lowest average level above sea level", isDone: false, answer: "Maldives" },
    { amount: 300, question: "This is city is situated in two continents", isDone: false, answer: "Istanbul, Turkey" },
    { amount: 400, question: "The Lord of the Rings Trilogy was filmed entirely in this country", isDone: false, answer: "New Zealand" }
]
  
export const questionsColumn4 = [
    { amount: 100, question: "Its the most streamed song of Mariah Carey on Spotify", isDone: false, answer: "All I Want for Christmas Is You" },
    { amount: 200, question: "Santa’s reindeer has the same name as another holiday mascot", isDone: false, answer: "Cupid" },
    { amount: 300, question: "It is the first company that used Santa Claus in advertising", isDone: false, answer: "Coca-Cola" },
    { amount: 400, question: "This place when baby Jesus born", isDone: false, answer: "Bethlehem" }
]